{
    "id": "a127a8f2918543bd856774313ebeaf5f",
    "title": "Active And Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "A song ......................................... by him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sung",
                "sang",
                "is sung"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The spider ............................................ by the boy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "killed",
                "was killed",
                "killing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Let him ..................................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "be helping",
                "be helped"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Maize ........................................ in the rainy season.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sown",
                "is sowing",
                "is sown"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Is a letter ..................................... by you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "been writing",
                "writing",
                "being written"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "A canal ................................................. by the workers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was digging",
                "was being dug",
                "been dug"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The job ................................................ (by me) by the end of this week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will finish",
                "will be finished",
                "will be finishing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Has your job ............................................ by you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "been finished",
                "finished",
                "been finishing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ......................................................... of his motherâ€™s death.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has informed",
                "has been informed",
                "was informing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "All the necessary precautions .............................................. by them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "were taking",
                "were taken",
                "have taken"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}